<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to Enable SSH on Ubuntu ? on Devops Monk</title>
    <link>https://devops-monk.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to Enable SSH on Ubuntu ? on Devops Monk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:05:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devops-monk.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HashiCorp Certified Terraform Associate</title>
      <link>https://devops-monk.com/2020/07/hashicorp-certified-terraform-associate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devops-monk.com/2020/07/hashicorp-certified-terraform-associate/</guid>
      <description>Finally, Terraform has announced the general availability of some of their Cloud Certifications like Terraform and Vault (and others to come like Consul).The exam is taken online with a live proctor. Its a mix of multiple-choices and “fill in the blanks” test with 57 questions for 1 hour.
Terraform associate is a foundational level of certification that evaluates your understanding of basic concepts and skills on Terraform OSS and the features exist on Terraform Cloud &amp;amp; Terraform Enterprise packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes practice questions for CKAD exam ?</title>
      <link>https://devops-monk.com/2020/07/kubernetes-practice-ckad-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devops-monk.com/2020/07/kubernetes-practice-ckad-exam/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes is an open-source system for automating deployment, scaling, and management of containerized applications. The CNCF/Linux Foundation offers this performance-based exam which targets the developer aspect of kubernetes skills such as deploying apps, configuring apps, rolling out the application, creating persistent volumes, etc.
Since this exam is performance-based rather than just multiple choice questions just knowing the concepts are not enough, we need a lot of practice before the exam. This article helps you understand, practice and get you ready for the exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Enable SSH on Ubuntu ?</title>
      <link>https://devops-monk.com/2020/07/how-to-enable-ssh-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devops-monk.com/2020/07/how-to-enable-ssh-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Secure Shell (SSH) is a protocol used to securely log onto remote machines. It is the most common way to access remote Linux servers.
1. Enabling SSH on Ubuntu The SSH server is not installed by default on Ubuntu desktop systems but it can be easily installed from the standard Ubuntu repositories.
To install and enable SSH on your Ubuntu system complete the following steps:
sudo apt-get install openssh-server
Once the installation is completed, the SSH service will start automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>